<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>nuutti.no</title><link>https://nuutti.no/</link><description>Recent content on nuutti.no</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://nuutti.no/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>fences.</title><link>https://nuutti.no/posts/fences/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nuutti.no/posts/fences/</guid><description>To me, a fence is a hostile piece of architecture.
Made to keep me out, but also made to keep someone in.
Why cant i go there. Why cant they come out.
Often a fence is more like a suggestion.
A local cemetary has a waist high fence all the way around it. If we assume that it is not to keep the dead people from getting out, then this fence seems like a futile attempt at keeping me from pissing on these graves.</description></item><item><title>e-mail</title><link>https://nuutti.no/posts/mail/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nuutti.no/posts/mail/</guid><description>RE: Superficial style of writing in emails. CC: your mom Hey, I have this certain superficial long winded style of writing emails. For some reason, i become suddenly more articulate, as i try to feign a sense of eloquence in my sentences. Even though i could have used fewer words, and you got all the necessary info you needed in one sentence, i will further elaborate on the one sentence, so that this email will fill some sort of arbitrary undefined length criteria that i have set for myself.</description></item><item><title>guest column 2</title><link>https://nuutti.no/posts/guest-column2/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nuutti.no/posts/guest-column2/</guid><description>This guest column is written by Amund.
I&amp;rsquo;ve known amund for years at this point, and I&amp;rsquo;ve lived with him for the last 2 years. He&amp;rsquo;s awesome, even when he wakes up annoyingly happy.
Amund is clever, funny and not least a great storyteller. He always finds himself in horrible situations that end up being a great story.
Here is his first time ever writing one of his stories down, i think it turned out great!</description></item><item><title>guest column</title><link>https://nuutti.no/posts/navn.tobias/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nuutti.no/posts/navn.tobias/</guid><description>This text is written by my dear friend Tobias.
Tobias is a smart man, even though he had the odds stacked against him by being born in Narvik.
He also plays the banjo really well, and if you ask me, thats one of the greatest instruments to learn.
I&amp;rsquo;ve only known Tobias for a semester or two, and i am so happy to have him as my friend.
He sometimes writes his thoughts down, just like i do.</description></item><item><title>worms</title><link>https://nuutti.no/posts/worms/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nuutti.no/posts/worms/</guid><description>No matter how hard i try, i cannot recall seeing a worm in years.
Where did the worms go?
Worms worms worms.</description></item><item><title>my feet are cold</title><link>https://nuutti.no/posts/cold-feet/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nuutti.no/posts/cold-feet/</guid><description>When they are not cold, i fear they will become cold.
If they freeze for long enough, the pain stops.
I do not want the pain to stop.
I do not fear the cold, i fear the absence of it.
I wear thick wool socks with some slippers, to create layers between me and the cold ground. I don&amp;rsquo;t want the cold world to contaminate me.
More layers.
When i finally achieve the perfect temperature, i rarely remember to notice it.</description></item><item><title>lightswitches.</title><link>https://nuutti.no/posts/buttons/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nuutti.no/posts/buttons/</guid><description>In my home i have the pleasure of flicking, cranking, pressing and twisting lightswitches.
Everyone knows the classic lightswitch. It&amp;rsquo;s a square switch, that you can flick on or off. It has a quite large surface area, no aiming required. The simple design with a large surface area, allows for the signature SLAP. This is quite simply the act of slapping the lightswitch.
Safely.
Light.
Area.
Promptly.
S.L.A.P.
Now let us move onto another classic lightswitch in Norway.</description></item><item><title>commitment issues.</title><link>https://nuutti.no/posts/commitment-issues/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nuutti.no/posts/commitment-issues/</guid><description>Commitment means saying yes for a future version of yourself.
And I am not that man!
For if i were, that would mean that the current version of myself is responsible for him.
That in turn, would require me to completely change how i view myself and the world.
AM I RESPONSIBLE FOR MYSELF AND MY FUTURE?!?!?
Who am I to make decisions for a Nuutti who i do not know yet?</description></item><item><title>i fell asleep with a book in my lap.</title><link>https://nuutti.no/posts/i-fell-asleep/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nuutti.no/posts/i-fell-asleep/</guid><description>And i woke up with the bookmark on the pillow next to me. My mind wants to ask the right questions, but all i can muster is a meager whimper:
&amp;ldquo;What happened last night?&amp;rdquo;
The bookmark replies with all the passion of a sexually liberated woman.
&amp;ldquo;You don&amp;rsquo;t remember? You took me out of the book and made love to me right here in this bed&amp;rdquo;
The book has fallen on the floor.</description></item><item><title>I've been accidentally biting the same part of my cheek for like 7 days. Ask me anything!</title><link>https://nuutti.no/posts/biting-my-cheek/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nuutti.no/posts/biting-my-cheek/</guid><description>The pain is excruciating. Please make this end.
I&amp;rsquo;m a 22 year old political science student, studying at NTNU, Trondheim in Norway.
It all started with a vegan spaghetti bolognese. One of my favourite meals to cook. It&amp;rsquo;s easy, cheap, and tasty.
And let me tell you this: I was starving.
In my hurry gorge down on this magnificent meal, i made a major techical flaw in my eating technique.</description></item><item><title>emotion theatre</title><link>https://nuutti.no/posts/emotion-theatre/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nuutti.no/posts/emotion-theatre/</guid><description>This is so freaking silly my dudes What the hell are we doing
Why cant i just fucking fart in the frozen pizza aisle??!? Out of all the aisles, that should definitely be the farting safe haven, right?
Why do we pretend that we dont fart?
Thats emotion, and flatulence thatre.
Why do we pretend that homeless people dont exist when we walk past them? What is the feeling we feel when we walk past someone like that?</description></item><item><title>beautiful piece of poetry</title><link>https://nuutti.no/posts/feel-like-this/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nuutti.no/posts/feel-like-this/</guid><description>Without any further ado, i present to you
Jordan Carter: No cap and gown, I ain&amp;rsquo;t go to class
I&amp;rsquo;d rather die before I come in last
I ain&amp;rsquo;t felt like this in a long time
I ain&amp;rsquo;t felt like this in a long time
I ain&amp;rsquo;t have shit in a long time
Just to feel like this it took a long time, yeah
Just to feel like this it took a long time, yeah</description></item><item><title>Snapchat usernames</title><link>https://nuutti.no/snapchat-name/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nuutti.no/snapchat-name/</guid><description>Snapchat is a litmus test social media In Norway, when i meet people who don&amp;rsquo;t use it, they are either too old or too cool for me.
&amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;d much rather just send a text or call you&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;You still use snapchat??&amp;rdquo;
In the rest of Europe, everyone just universally agrees on using whatsapp.
My own mother doesn&amp;rsquo;t pick up the phone unless i call her on Whatsapp.
A few weeks ago, she had her birthday, i called her 2 days late.</description></item><item><title>A really funny predicament for real</title><link>https://nuutti.no/posts/a-day-in-my-life/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nuutti.no/posts/a-day-in-my-life/</guid><description>Today i tried to get out of bed for 2 hours. After all, i study political science, so it&amp;rsquo;s not like i actually have to do anything.
No reason to get out of bed. LOL!!
I have lost all discipline i once had. LOL im such a lazy slob now! LOOOLLL
I go to my kitchen, and realise i&amp;rsquo;m out of coffee filters. Since i am a man of solutions, i make a coffee with toilet paper as a filter.</description></item><item><title>A hard conversation with a toothbrush</title><link>https://nuutti.no/posts/breaking-up-with-a-toothbrush/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nuutti.no/posts/breaking-up-with-a-toothbrush/</guid><description>Maybe you&amp;rsquo;re just a toothbrush, and maybe I&amp;rsquo;m just overthinking. But i&amp;rsquo;ve been meaning to tell you&amp;hellip; I&amp;rsquo;m breaking up with you
Its not you. Its me. Well, actually -
It&amp;rsquo;s a 100% you. You&amp;rsquo;re&amp;hellip; Old&amp;hellip; And frankly i don&amp;rsquo;t know what i ever saw in you.
I&amp;rsquo;ve found NEW a brush with bristles that look shiny, and straight.
Your bristles are all fucked up and fuzzy. You&amp;rsquo;re not the brush i once picked at the store.</description></item><item><title>HAPPY SPOOKTOBER</title><link>https://nuutti.no/posts/happy-spooktober/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nuutti.no/posts/happy-spooktober/</guid><description>the SPOOKIEST MONTH OF THE YEAAARRRRR Spooky scary skeletons.
Spooky scary skeletons with pumpkin heads.
Scary stuff on Halloween
Leaves on trees are literally becoming yellow and DYING.
Shoutout to all my spooky bois and girls out there</description></item><item><title>DO NOT EAT A WHOLE BAG OF SPINACH IN ONE SITTING</title><link>https://nuutti.no/posts/do-not-eat-a-whole-bag-of-spinach/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nuutti.no/posts/do-not-eat-a-whole-bag-of-spinach/</guid><description>Jesus christ! My gut flora is committing mutiny!</description></item><item><title>Going up the country</title><link>https://nuutti.no/posts/going-up-the-country/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nuutti.no/posts/going-up-the-country/</guid><description>by Canned Heat.
Great song indeed.
It reminds me of the discussions I&amp;rsquo;ve had with jævla søringa.
So many people from Oslo consider Trondheim as the first city of northern norway. But that doesn&amp;rsquo;t make any sense at all. I am currently, in late september basking in the southern sun beaming upon my forehead. Do you ever feel self counscious about the size or shape of your forehead?
Me neither.</description></item><item><title>On starving</title><link>https://nuutti.no/posts/starving/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nuutti.no/posts/starving/</guid><description>811 million people. 10% of everyone on this planet go hungry regularly. Thats fucking nuts, man.
I usually end up starving because of my own stupidity.
I am my own worst enemy.
Sundays. Sundays are my &amp;ldquo;starving days&amp;rdquo;
Usually i wake up feeling as one should feel on a lovely sunday morning.
Super mega ultra hungover.
I&amp;rsquo;m not gonna lie. I should probably maybe drink less.
Sometimes when i wake up, i catch myself wondering: Am i ever going to feel hydrated again?</description></item><item><title>Rød</title><link>https://nuutti.no/posts/roed/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nuutti.no/posts/roed/</guid><description>Todays blogpost is special, but only because it&amp;rsquo;s not special AT ALL. Todays topic is so impressively, and UTTERLY un-interesting.
It&amp;rsquo;s the first color of the rainbow, from the top down.
The colour of blood, hell, and pain.
But simultaniously also the colour of love.
Ah, the duality of red!
The colour of leftist politics in europe, but then across the pond red is associated with the republicans.
It&amp;rsquo;s ironic how communists and MAGA lunatics have this strong colour in common.</description></item><item><title>Kirkegata 61a experience</title><link>https://nuutti.no/posts/kirkegata-61a-experience/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nuutti.no/posts/kirkegata-61a-experience/</guid><description>Kirkegata 61a experience. Omgivelse + cast Når man synker ned i kjelleren, forbi den råtne mugghula som har varmtvannstanken vår, glemme man fort at det e sol ute. I kjellern e det alltid mørkt. I kjellern blir man truffet av en vegg med egglukt, da hele kollektivet spiser hovedsakelig stekte egg, til hvert eneste måltid. Veggene har samme gulfarge som en hvit tskjorte som har blitt svetta og smurt med solkrem.</description></item><item><title>HELLO WORLD</title><link>https://nuutti.no/posts/my-first-post/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nuutti.no/posts/my-first-post/</guid><description>My first post This website is my digital canvas.
However, i will not be doing any art, or painting for that matter! (well, perhaps?) I will be spewing my thoughts, into the void, for the world wide web to see. There will be (un)funny stories, how to&amp;rsquo;s, and whatever else comes out of my brain. Completely unprocessed and raw.
I will be vomiting ideas onto this digital canvas.
Spraying my non-intellectual diarrhea into this cesspool we call the internet.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://nuutti.no/gallery/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nuutti.no/gallery/</guid><description>pictures taken on my nokia3310 (2017version)</description></item><item><title/><link>https://nuutti.no/lore/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nuutti.no/lore/</guid><description>what is going on? i am human. i need no introduction.
But here you have one anyway:
In the far north, decades ago, during a beautiful summer morning something amazing happened. A small, loud, screaming human emerged from the womb of my mother.
That screaming human was me.
I&amp;rsquo;ve been screaming ever since.
I&amp;rsquo;m a 22 year old guy. I like talking &amp;amp; thinking.
This website is a window into my unprocessed thoughts.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://nuutti.no/posts/understandconservatives/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nuutti.no/posts/understandconservatives/</guid><description>it boils down to morals
During my time in university I have learned so much.
I&amp;rsquo;ve learned how to run with a sickpack of beer without shaking the cans.
Stabilized beer running. ✔️
I&amp;rsquo;ve learned how to be the worst neighbour. The key is to NOT turn down the volume.
worst neighbour ever ✔️
I&amp;rsquo;ve learned how to burn spaghetti. The recipe is quite simple:
An inadequate amount of water mixed with Extreme amounts of spaghetti combined with the aboslute highest heat setting Results guaranteed.</description></item></channel></rss>