<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Posts on I am nuutti.no</title><link>https://nuutti.no/posts/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on I am nuutti.no</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://nuutti.no/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Rød</title><link>https://nuutti.no/posts/roed/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nuutti.no/posts/roed/</guid><description>Todays blogpost is special, but only because it&amp;rsquo;s not special AT ALL. Todays topic is so impressively, and UTTERLY un-interesting.
It&amp;rsquo;s the first color of the rainbow, from the top down.
The colour of blood, hell, and pain.
But simultaniously also the colour of love.
Ah, the duality of red!
The colour of leftist politics in europe, but then across the pond red is associated with the republicans.
It&amp;rsquo;s ironic how communists and MAGA lunatics have this strong colour in common.</description></item><item><title>Kirkegata 61a experience</title><link>https://nuutti.no/posts/kirkegata-61a-experience/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nuutti.no/posts/kirkegata-61a-experience/</guid><description>Kirkegata 61a experience. Omgivelse + cast Når man synker ned i kjelleren, forbi den råtne mugghula som har varmtvannstanken vår, glemme man fort at det e sol ute. I kjellern e det alltid mørkt. I kjellern blir man truffet av en vegg med egglukt, da hele kollektivet spiser hovedsakelig stekte egg, til hvert eneste måltid. Veggene har samme gulfarge som en hvit tskjorte som har blitt svetta og smurt med solkrem.</description></item><item><title>HELLO WORLD</title><link>https://nuutti.no/posts/my-first-post/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nuutti.no/posts/my-first-post/</guid><description>My first post This website is my digital canvas.
However, i will not be doing any art, or painting for that matter! (well, perhaps?) I will be spewing my thoughts, into the void, for the world wide web to see. There will be (un)funny stories, how to&amp;rsquo;s, and whatever else comes out of my brain. Completely unprocessed and raw.
I will be vomiting ideas onto this digital canvas.
Spraying my non-intellectual diarrhea into this cesspool we call the internet.</description></item></channel></rss>